A person's soul continues
to live on after death.
Previously on Fringe...
And all we have to do is summon
the soul to the host
and he'll be back here
with us.
Soul magnets.
William is gone.
You can't bring him back.
The soul magnets...drew
your consciousness into Olivia.
I assure you
she is totally safe.
Olivia's brain can...
accommodate my consciousness
for...several weeks.
Weeks?
Not a chance.
48 hours.
Then I want you
out of my agent
or I'll have Dr. Bishop
figure out how to drive you out.
The little old lady
from Iipanina.
It's The Girl From Ipanema.
And no.
Try again.
Oh, Walter, can you
try something else?
You're taking
the fun out of it.
What's the temperature,
son?
We're at 64 degrees.
Perfect!
Astrid, are we ready?
Just about, Wally.
- And you're sure this is safe, Walter.
- Perfectly.
If everything goes
according to plan,
the electrical current
will latch onto
the dominant consciousness
which is Belly's
and coax it
into its new residence.
I meant safe
for Olivia.
Oh. Of course.
- No offense.
- Oh. None taken.
Olivia's mind
is still peacefully at rest.
She won't be aware
of any of this.
Though we should all take
a few steps back.
Excuse me?
It's perfectly safe, son.
I assure you.
EEGs are online.
You ready, Belly?
Aye, aye, Captain.
Do it, dear.
Okay.
Three, two, one...
Walter?
Didn't work.
Damn!
You can reset
the circuit breakers, dear.
Tell the medical school
we're returning Mr. Spencer.
Sorry.
So what now?
Well, now I guess
we try and find
another brain-dead host.
And what makes you think
it's gonna go any better
this time?
That body
fit all of your parameters,
and we were lucky
to find him in the first place.
Perhaps we should
think up another idea.
I have a new idea.
You said that if you didn't
find a suitable host in 48 hours
that you would
just go away.
Are you suggesting
that I die?
I'm suggesting
that I want Olivia back.
And I'm losing patience.
Peter--oh, Peter,
help me!
Astrid!
What happened?
Call 911.
Female. 31 years old.
Tonic-clonic seizures.
No response
to 4 milligrams Lorazepam IV.
BP's 190 over 110.
Trauma bay two!
Pupils dilated.
- How long has she been seizing?
- Going on 20 minutes.
25.
Okay. Start her on
a phenytoin drip.
- No, that's absolutely wrong!
- Excuse me?
Gentlemen, you need to step
outside unless you're family.
- She's my girlfriend.
- He's my partner.
Walter-- William cannot tolerate
phenytoin--he's anemic!
She's crashing.
Let's defib at 360.
Too much!
It's too much.
What if his consciousness
uh--uh--uh...
Changed her physiology?
A charge that size
directly into her heart--
Walter, they have
to do something.
354. Charge to 360.
Doctor...
I've been jolted once today.
If you do it again...
You will kill me
and the young woman
I'm living inside of.
♪ Fringe 3x19 ♪
Lysergic Acid Diethylamide
Original Air Date on April 15, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
How could this have happened.
Dr. Bell, you assured me that
Agent Dunham was perfectly safe.
And I believed
that she was.
With the rats,
it was nearly two weeks
before I began to see
any complications.
What rats?
My test subjects.
When I was first conducting
soul magnet experiments
30 years ago.
The rats lasted nearly two weeks
before the host's
consciousness got lost.
I never anticipated
that it would happen
more quickly in a human.
Wait. Go back.
What do you mean,
with the rats the host
consciousness got lost?
It seems that
at a certain point
the brain can no longer
accommodate
two people's consciousness.
So one just went away.
And no matter how hard
I tried,
I was unable to retrieve it.
You gave me your word.
48 hours.
You said if you didn't find
a suitable host in 48 hours--
I know what you're
going to suggest, young man.
Peter's already
said as much.
But as much
as I may want to...
I can no longer
simply leave.
And why not?
Because at this point,
your consciousness
is the only thing
keeping Olivia's
body alive.
- That's right.
- Walter...
How long before
Olivia's gone for good?
Well...
I don't know exactly,
but based on
what we've seen thus far,
I would say...
No more than...
a day.
Well...Well, if we're
going to get Olivia back,
we're not going to
do it here.
Okay...what about this?
What if we try
to activate her chi?
Acupuncture?
Yes. We try and stimulate
her seventh chakra.
Pure consciousness.
As much as I love
the notion,
it could take
dozens of sessions
spread over several days.
You said we had to find
a way to pull Olivia out
in 24 hours.
What if we don't?
Have to find a way
to pull her out, I mean.
What are you thinking?
What if, instead of
trying to find a way
to pull Olivia out,
we try and find a way
to go in?
- Peter...
- I'm just saying consider it.
We know he has a healthy ego.
You don't start a company like
Massive Dynamic without an ego.
But do you really think
that he would let Olivia die
just so--
he could go on living?
I don't know.
Maybe, maybe not.
But on the list of
accomplishments
for William Bell,
cheating death would
certainly rank number one.
Hmm.
Kids.
We think that we
have found a way
to bring
Olivia's mind back.
And to remove William's.
Whole brain emulation.
It's another one of
Belly's old projects.
It describes
how an inorganic host
can house organic material.
We're gonna put Belly
in the computer.
Much to do and not much time.
While we go into
Olivia's mind,
you can get to work
on this.
It's very self-explanatory.
Enter Olivia's mind how?
We've done it before--
when Olivia and Agent Scott
shared the dream state.
It's a simple variation.
Walter.
Every brain generates
a quantifiable electric field.
If we can...
Tune ours precisely
to Olivia's,
then we can share her mind.
We can go looking for her.
- Walter?
- Hmm?
Where do you keep
the neurosensors?
Back shelf
by the fish food.
If I remember
correctly,
you had to put
an electromagnetic probe
into her brain
and dose her
with a massive amount
of hallucinogenics.
LSD!
That could solve
the superego problem.
Ohh... Oh, that is
brilliant, son!
This may be a weird
time to ask,
but have you
ever tripped?
- Are you suggesting that--
- Of course!
It's Olivia's mind
we're entering.
Presumably,
it will be some
maze-like iteration
of her psyche.
Memories are subconscious.
You know her better than anyone.
If she is lost in her mind,
we need you to guide us.
Astrid!
We need to mix up
2,000 milligrams of LSD
and--and we need
some sugar cubes. Please.
You first, son.
Don't be nervous.
I imagine there are
things in this very lab
that are as mind-blowing
as anything that I've
experienced while tripping.
Besides...
This is merely a conduit
to Olivia's mind.
And when we get there,
we should all be very cogent.
In 30 to 45 minutes...
But I've added an accelerant.
You can start to prepare
the sedative, dear.
I'll go and help Belly.
Peter, don't worry.
I'll keep my eye
on the monitors.
I'll make sure
you're okay.
It's not me
I'm worried about.
I'm pretty sure
there's a good reason
why we can't enter
each other's minds.
What if we kick something
loose in there?
Right now,
I think you're
her only hope.
How's it coming?
So far so good.
What?
You're bald.
I think
he's an observer.
It's okay, Peter.
Walter, we're ready.
Oh. Good.
Bring him over.
It's okay.
Drugs?
Yep. Lots of 'em.
Whew.
Ooh...
That tickles.
Peter!
Over here!
I think you better
help me down.
Whoa...Whoa!
No! No! No!
Of all the places
to grab a man,
you choose the crotch
of my pants!
Hey, I broke
your fall, didn't I?
You spared me no embarrassment
in the process.
I thought you said
none of this was real anyway.
I said that everything
is a product
of Olivia's subconscious.
My feelings
are most definitely real.
Where's Belly?
I have no idea.
He must have entered
somewhere else.
It doesn't matter.
We're here for Olivia anyway.
So what's the next step
in the plan?
There is one,
right, Walter?
Please tell me that
the plan doesn't end here.
Of course not!
The plan...
is to find Olivia
and guide her out.
We just have to
start looking.
Wal--
Walter!
Amazing, isn't it?
How are we supposed
to pick Olivia out?
All these people are dressed
like they raided her closet.
More likely,
she equipped them
according
to her preferences.
Our fault, I fear.
Cortexiphan subjects
experience a strong desire
to blend in,
to stay in the background.
They were designed
that way.
Designed that way?
Peter.
What is that?
I believe it's morse code.
And unless I'm mistaken,
that's an S.O.S.
What are you doing?
Chocolate pudding.
My favorite.
Ah, come on, Walter,
you can't seriously be thinking
about eating right now.
Of course not.
I just had lunch.
What are you saying?
I'm asking who it is.
It's Olivia!
She's found us.
Tell her to stay there.
We're on our way.
Any changes?
No.
They all seem oddly
peaceful.
Do you really think
it's possible
to upload a person's
consciousness to a computer?
I don't know.
I'm just following
Bell's instructions.
The aim
is for the computer
to mimic the behavior
of neurons.
I never understood
why Walter
was so drawn to licorice.
But look at it.
The swirl...
It's Bernini's
spiral altar at St. Peter's.
It...doesn't end.
Did you clean that up?
Yeah.
I thought I'd help you
clear the table.
You touched the tray
with the sugar cubes?
Sure.
Why?
Have you ever taken
LSD?
The towers
are out of proportion.
We should be closer
by now.
It's Olivia's mind
assigning importance.
Our surroundings represent
her emotional landscape,
don't forget.
Oh. Oh, my.
Olivia's stepfather.
What? Where?
Over there!
That's--that's him!
Olivia's stepfather.
Hmm.
Walter, I'm...
Getting a bad feeling
about this.
Any suggestions?
Yes.
Run!
Oh!
The cab!
Wait, wait, wait.
You're driving?
Okay.
What the hell was that?
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Peter...I made a skid.
There. The elevators.
Walter! Peter.
Hello.
Nina! Are you a sight
for sore eyes!
We're looking for
Olivia.
Olivia?
We think she's in an office
near the top
on the north side.
Walter thinks
it's Bell's office.
Okay.
This elevator
is the fastest one.
It will take you directly
to the private lobby
of the upper floors.
- Walter!
- Oh!
Whoa--
okay.
She tried to kill us.
You saw.
Why is everyone trying
to kill us?
I don't like
this place.
Me neither.
Olivia?
You in there?
Careful, Peter.
We don't know
what her mind's put
on the other side
of this door.
We should be ready
for anything.
Belly.
I lied.
Olivia's not here.
I was concerned
if you knew it was just me,
Peter wouldn't let you
come rescue me.
Belly...
Why are you a cartoon?
I'd ask yourselves
the same question.
I found myself
on the street,
but neither of you
were nearby.
And then a car
tried to run me down.
So I came here.
I assumed it would be
a safe haven...
But then I encountered Nina.
I don't understand.
If this is all
a projection of Olivia's mind,
why is everything
turning against us?
When she came to us in the lab,
she asked for help.
What I'm starting to think
is that when my mind
entered hers,
her ego became confused--
her sense of self.
Which, in turn,
initiated the darker part
of her subconscious
allowing her deepest
fears to run rampant.
Explain that.
We're saying
that Olivia is not aware
that Belly's consciousness
entered hers.
As far as she's concerned,
one minute she was fine,
the next minute
she was set adrift
in her innermost thoughts.
It's her fears that are
causing the siege.
Then, in that case,
she's not lost, she's hiding.
That's what she does.
When Olivia is afraid,
she retreats.
That's not good.
And being lost is?
Yes, it's better.
I expected there to be
a logical trail
whereby we could
track her
because Olivia
wanted to be found.
If she's hiding...
I'm afraid we're looking
for a needle in a haystack.
He's right, son.
Everything in her mind
is dangerous
and hostile to her now.
How can we expect to find her
if she's frightened
of everything, us included?
Because she'd do exactly
what you did--
she'll find a place
that she considers to be safe.
And she'll hide out.
There's an entire world
out there
with no rhyme or reason.
Where would you
like to start?
♪ ♪
Hey...
Hey.
I know you said
only water,
but...
It might be good
if you can eat something.
But if you want,
I can take it away.
That's fine too.
Whatever you like.
Thank you...
For this.
What you're feeling
right now.
It's just the effects
of the LSD.
But it's temporary.
No.
It's infinite.
It's all around us.
You didn't see that.
I didn't see that.
But now I know.
And I know it followed me.
What followed you?
Death.
I saw death.
All of it.
And it was me.
Can you hold my hand?
Please.
♪ ♪
Well, Peter?
The first place I would look
is Jacksonville.
Jacksonville's
the last place she'd go.
Exactly. That's my point.
I know Olivia.
She knows that that's
the last place
anybody would look
for her.
We only have so much time,
Peter. Are you sure?
Yes.
Let's get to Jacksonville.
I assume that's about us.
The Zeppelin.
Peter!
Come on, son!
We should circumnavigate
the currents.
I should have known.
Should have known what,
Walter?
When we were over there...
Getting Peter back,
and we were on that stage...
You said good-bye to me.
I should have known
you had no intentions
of dying that day.
As long as I've known you,
you've hated good-byes.
I guess that's true.
I need you, William.
I don't know what to do.
About Peter.
About the machine.
About what's waiting
for him...
For the world
because of what we did.
Walter, when we were young
and foolish
with too much power
and too many dreams
that no one could stand
in the way of...
We needed each other.
I don't understand.
We needed each other then,
to check and balance.
And now?
Now you possess
the wisdom of humility.
We didn't back then.
The decisions you make
will be the right ones.
The direction you choose
to take will be just.
What's that?
Fuel gauge.
How many
are up there?
It's just me.
This is a flare gun.
You don't want to get
shot with a flare gun.
Peter--
Walter, stay back!
Who are you?
What's your name?
Peter.
Peter what?
Peter Bishop.
Nice to meet you.
Peter!
Peterrr!
Walter!
Ahh!
You're here with us.
You're back in the lab.
It's all right.
I'm back.
Oh, damn.
Your father'll be fine, Peter.
He knows there's no time
to come back.
And even if he tried,
he would never find us.
We're on our own.
Who was that guy?
Someone unpleasant
from her past, I imagine.
This way.
We'll need to take
possession of a vehicle.
Do you drive
a motorcycle?
I would love to ride
on a motorcycle.
Hold on.
You're going
the wrong way.
I've got ten years
of experience in Jacksonville.
We're on East Union Street.
It leads
to the Matthews' Expressway.
If you want to get to the
Jacksonville Day Care Center--
She won't be
at the day care center.
We need to go that way.
I thought you said
she was that way.
And I thought you said you
wanted to travel by motorcycle.
The computer's nearly ready to
receive Belly's consciousness.
Hand me those tubes, dear.
This should snap right in.
Damn my hands!
Walter, it's okay.
I can get you another one.
There isn't another one.
I'll have to modify
the ECL 82 tube
from my phonograph.
And I'll need tinfoil
and instant glue
and a 60-watt light bulb.
And hurry, dear!
Where are we going,
Peter?
Olivia told me she lived
on the military base!
Olivia once told me
that she sometimes thinks
about what it would be like
to just be normal.
She said she falls
asleep sometimes
thinking about what it
would be like
if her life hadn't taken
the turn that it did.
She told me that the last
time she remembered
feeling that way
was the day before
she met you and Walter
at the cortexiphan trials.
I think she's
down there somewhere.
In that house, on that day.
Hiding out.
They're all the same.
How will we find her?
Her real dad painted
the door red.
He told her
that it was good luck.
The army told them it was
against regulations,
but he was an important man,
so they let it slide.
There aren't many
streets left, Peter.
Maybe the door
was painted green again
after they moved away.
It wasn't.
What are you waiting for?
What if I'm wrong?
What if she's not in there?
I've taken us
so far off course...
You should have thought
of that
back at the Zeppelin.
Peter.
Olivia.
It's okay.
I'm so afraid.
I don't know
what's happening.
There are all these
people trying to hurt me,
and this was the safest
place I knew.
I know,
and I'm here to help you.
But we don't have
a lot of time,
so I can't
explain it all right now,
but I need you
to understand that you're safe.
It's okay for you
to come back.
Peter?
What's wrong?
Peter,
you're scaring me.
You're not her.
What are you
talking about?
This is not you.
I can see it
in your eyes.
It's not you.
I just needed to know
it was you.
Olivia?
People have been
tricking me,
but I knew the real you
would recognize me.
Oh, no.
♪ ♪
Run!
Peter, this way!
Peter?
Peter, Peter, Peter!
Peter, Peter, Peter, it's okay!
Calm down, son!
Walter!
Walter, she's here.
I found her!
She's here!
I gotta go back, Walter.
Shh, shh, shh.
I gotta go back. They're gonna get her.
Walter, what do I do?
Nothing, dear.
Nothing.
All we can do is wait.
It's up to Belly now.
Come on, breathe.
In and out.
Hey...Hey...
Hey...
Oh, I lost her.
I lost her.
♪ ♪
Go!
No more.
I'm not afraid of you.
How?
I suspect I know
what has happened here.
I think my experiment
was right after all.
You should have been safe
inside your mind...
Except it's you,
and you have never felt safe.
You are your own
worst enemy, Olivia.
You took the opportunity
to let your fears overwhelm you,
but you just fought back.
In the end, you are as strong
as Walter and I
always believed you were.
And now you know it too.
So what happens now?
Now, you go back.
But not me.
For you to survive,
I need to leave.
I don't understand.
You don't have to.
Well, that's Walter.
Right on time.
Please tell Walter that I knew
the dog wouldn't hunt.
Olivia?
Hi.
You lie there
and rest.
One consciousness.
One glorious consciousness!
What happened to me?
What do you remember?
I remember you.
And I remember
William Bell was there.
Walter.
It didn't work.
He's gone.
William's gone.
Walter...
I think Bell
gave me a message.
He said tell Walter
that I knew the dog
wouldn't hunt.
Walter,
what does that mean?
When we would do
experiments,
he would
use that expression
when he knew something
wouldn't work.
But he suggested the computer.
It was his idea.
Exactly.
He knew he wasn't
coming out.
And he hates good-byes.
Welcome back, Olivia.
Thank you.
Walter?
I downloaded Zoom
for you.
♪ come on and
zoom zoom zoom-a zoom ♪
I can watch it
with you if you'd like.
♪ Zoom zoom zoom-a zoom ♪
♪ everybody's doing it,
everybody ♪
If you don't mind...
I'd just like to be alone
for a while longer.
Okay.
Take your time.
Well, you look better
than the last time I saw you.
Yeah. It's amazing
what a couple of hours
will do for a guy.
Hi.
You hungry?
Uh, no.
I'm okay, thanks.
So how you feeling?
Um...
I feel like
I've just woken up
from a really
strange dream.
Thank you
for coming to get me.
It's not as dangerous
as crossing into
another universe, but I try.
You're welcome.
What are we gonna have
to deal with next, right?
I don't know.
But for some reason,
I'm not afraid
to move forward anymore.
Sure you don't want
some toast?
No, I--no, I'm fine.
Who is this guy?
I saw him in your mind.
You had him locked up
in a Zeppelin.
He was just flying around
trapped in there.
I don't know.
I haven't seen him before.
But I think that he's the man
who's gonna kill me.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net